{
    "subject": "resource/Benjamin_Franklin",
    "predicate": "ontology/child",
    "object": "resource/Sarah_Franklin_Bache",
    "human_readable": "Benjamin Franklin had a child named Sarah Franklin Bache.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9658894538879395,
            "question": "Was Sarah Franklin Bache related to Benjamin Franklin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.892503559589386,
            "question": "Who was Benjamin Franklin's child?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8325936794281006,
            "question": "Who was Benjamin Franklin's daughter named after?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8290995359420776,
            "question": "Name one of Benjamin Franklin's children."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7723947167396545,
            "question": "What was the name of Benjamin Franklin's daughter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7649954557418823,
            "question": "Who was Sarah Franklin Bache's father?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7426167726516724,
            "question": "What is the name of Benjamin Franklin's daughter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7401173710823059,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Benjamin Franklin and Sarah Franklin Bache?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6492131352424622,
            "question": "Did Benjamin Franklin have any children?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6147751808166504,
            "question": "How many children did Benjamin Franklin have?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Benjamin Franklin had a child named Sarah Franklin Bache.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7020_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Benjamin Franklin have any children?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7020_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Benjamin Franklin and Sarah Franklin Bache?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7020_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Benjamin Franklin's daughter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7020_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7020_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7020_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7020_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7020_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7020_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7020_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7020_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7020_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7020_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7020_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Sarah Franklin was indeed the mother of Sarah Franklin Bache, confirming that Benjamin Franklin had a child named Sarah Franklin Bache."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}